Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 9, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Une Etape, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Programme d'Action Syndical, Rapport d'Orientation, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Alais, Froges et Canargue: Ce que vous devez savoir, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Compagnie de Produits Chimiqueset Camargue
  - Item 3: Remuneration du Travail, 1945; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Remuneration du Travail II, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Remuneration du Travail III, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Force Ouvriere: Le 'Drame' Confederal, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Force Ouvriere
  - Item 7: L'Unite, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Les Responsables de la Scission demasques, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Syndique, Sois un Syndicaliste, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Le Droit Syndical avec un exemplaire de ststuts-typeSyndicats, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: L'Organisation de la C.G.T.-F.O. et du Mouvement Syndical, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: La Participation Ouvrier aux benefices: arme de combat du patronat, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Federation des Travailleurs de la Metallurgie; Henri Jourdain
  - Item 13: Les Conges Payes, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Nos Cahiers (Etatisme ou Democrtie Economique, + sev arts), 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Rapport d'Activite (1938-1946) de la C.G.T., Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Benoit Frachon
  - Item 16: Rapport sur l'Activite Internationale de la C.G.T., 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Louis Saillant
- Box: 9, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How Strong Are the French Communists?, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Les Scissions Syndicales, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: L'Administration du Syndicat, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Le Comite d'Entreprise - Organisme d'Avenir, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: Federation des Travailleurs de la MetallurgieColonies
  - Item 5: Cinquieme Cycle d'Etudes des Techniques de Direction du Personnel, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: CEGOS
  - Item 6: Nos Cahiers (Cadres ou Militants, + several articles), 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: Comite d'etudes techniques economiques et sociales
  - Item 7: Nos Cahiers (Prepares le Lendemain en VivantMeme, + sev arts), 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ou va la C.G.T.? Lettre d'un ancien a quelques jeunesgalons, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: Pierre Monatte
  - Item 9: Statuts modifies au XXVI Congres National, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Nos Cahiers, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Box: 9, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Le Probleme de l'emploi et du chomage dans les theories economiques, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles Bettelheim
  - Item 2: Reponse Francaise au questionnaire de l'Organisationlong terme, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Organisation for European Economic Co-operation
  - Item 3: Le Mouvement des Prox de 1939 a 1949, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor Keeps Left in France, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Ogier Preteceille
  - Item 5: Rapport sur la Reforme de l'Enterprise, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: French Trade Unions and Their Membership, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Ambassador de France
- Box: 9, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Les Comites d'Entreprise, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Danel
  - Item 2: Jules Guesde et Les Greves, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Author: Jules Guesde
  - Item 3: Producteurs (Prime a la Production dans les industries chimiques), 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Author: L'Institut Technique des Salaires
  - Item 4: Producteurs (Prime a la Production dans les industries chimiques), 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Producteurs (Prix Normal et Cout Reel...et l'attribution du profit), 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Box: 9, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: L'Entreprise Moderne, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Author: Francois Clement
  - Item 2: Formalites Sociales, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Guide de l'Adminstrateur de Syndicat, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Author: Confederation Generale du Travail Force Ouvriere
  - Item 4: Guide du Contremaitre, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Rapport sur le Reglement Interieur, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Programme de Redressement Economique et Sociale, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Les Resolutions adoptees par le XXVII Congres de la C.G.T., 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Les Conseils de Prud'Hommes, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Notre Combat, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Nationalization in France and Italy, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Author: Mario Einaudi
  - Item 11: Social Security in France, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Author: France. Ministere du travail
- Box: 9, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Guide du Militant, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Le Fichier Confederal de Documentation, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Le Logement, 1949; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Le Mouvement Syndical et La Lutte pour le Bien-etre et la Liberte, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Le Travail des Femmes, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: L'Education Ouvriere, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: Georges Vidalenc
  - Item 7: L'Efficience Americaine, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: G.A. Panier
  - Item 8: L'Efficience Americaine, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: L'Evolution du Pouvoir d'Achat, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: Bureau d'Etudes et de Documentationet Syndicales
  - Item 10: Organisation Professionnelle, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Orientations Economiques, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Reequipement et Finncement, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: Centre des jeunes patrons
  - Item 13: Revue Francaise du Travail: Organisation du Ministre duSociale, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: France. Ministe`re du travail et de la securite sociale
  - Item 14: Sans Plan Marshall Pas de Plan Monnet, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert Champion
  - Item 15: Social Security in France, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: The Truth About the French Miners' Strike, 1948; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Une Nouvelle Notion du Salaire, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Box: 9, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Producteurs: Prix Normal et Cout Reel...et l'attribution du profit: Quatrieme fascicule: Principes de gestion des prix sur la base du cout normal, 1952; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Producteurs: Prix Normal et Cout Reel...et l'attribution du profit: Troisieme fascicule: Mesure de la production, 1951; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Producteurs: Prix Normal et Cout Reel...et l'attribution du profit: Deuxieme fascicule: Plus-valve mensuelle d'exploitation et normes de productivite collective, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Simplification du Travail, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Box: 9, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Conventions Collectives de Travail, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Author: Eugene Muller; Jean paul Murcier
  - Item 2: French Views on Communism, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: La Remuneration du Travail et La Politique du Salaire, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Author: Institut de Science Economique Appliquee
  - Item 4: Le Premier Mai, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Proudhon, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Author: Maurice Dommanget
  - Item 6: La Charte de l'Habitat, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Albert Thierry, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Box: 9, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Traite du Contentieux de la Securite Sociale, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Author: Claude Peignot
  - Item 2: Des 'Modes de Remuneration' aux 'Reformes de l'Entreprise', 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Author: Revue Economique Franco-Suisse
  - Item 3: France and the Problem of Productivity, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Guide de l'Employer: Securite Sociale, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: La Politique Francaise de l'Habitation, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Author: Robert Bordaz
  - Item 6: La Remuneration Facteur de Productivite, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Box: 9, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Les Conges Payes: Commentaire methodique etla legislation, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Author: Louis Boiteau
  - Item 2: Producteurs (L'Annee des Techniques Salaires dans le Monde:, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Hommes-Rouages ou Hommes Libres?, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Humanisme du Travail et Humanites, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Author: Georges Friedmann
  - Item 5: Voici les Faits: On parle de chomage, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Author: Association de la Libre Entreprise
- Box: 9, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Producteurs (La Gestion des Salaires dans les entreprises), 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: La Formation Professionnelle, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Notes: pt. I
  - Item 3: La Qualification Professionnelle, 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Notes: pt. II
  - Item 4: Producteurs (L'Institution des Primes Collectives dans les entreprises), 1950; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Box: 9, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Allgemeine Geschichte des Sozialismus und der Sozialen Kampfe, 1921; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Author: Max Beer
  - Item 2: Der Sozialismus einft und jekt, 1922; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Deutscher Reichsanzeiger und Breubischer Staatsanzeiger, 1938; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Die kulturelle und volkswirtschaftliche Bedeutung der Gewerkschaften: Rede in der Versammlung der Berliner Gewerkschaftsfunktionare am 15. September 1926swirtschaftliche Bedeutung der Gewerkschaften, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Die Sozialistische Arbeiterjugend: Zeile und Aufgaben, 1929; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Praktische Gewerkschafts-Bildung, 1927; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Warum Arm Sein?, 1929; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Zur Organisation Unserer Jugendarbeit, 1926; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Box: 9, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Arbeitsbericht der Industriegewerkschaft BAU Grok-Berlin, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Arbeitsrichtlinien fur den Fachbuch-Lektor, 1941; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Germany. Reichsministerium fur Volksaufklarung und Propaganda
  - Item 3: Was sind Gewerkschaften?, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: August Enderle
  - Item 4: Der Wiederaufbau der Bayerischen Wirtschaft imWirtschaft, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Kommunistische Partei Deutschlands. Landesbezirk Bayern. Wirtschaftskommission
  - Item 5: Germany, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Federation of the German Trade-Unions
  - Item 6: Het Marshall-Plan verschaft werk, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Sozialaufbau und regionale Wirstschaftsplanung, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Status and Prospects of German Trade-Unions and Works Councils, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: United States. Dept. of State. Office of Intelligence Research. Division of Research for Europe
  - Item 9: Wo stehen wir Wohin gehen wir? Der Historische Auftrag der SPD, 1945; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Otto Grotewohl
- Box: 9, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Bedeutung und Zukunftige Aufgaben der Arbeiterbewegung, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Author: Franz Josef Furtwangler
  - Item 2: Der Neue Kampf Um Freiheit: Briefe und DokumenteSozialisten, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Author: American Association for a Democratic Germany. Research Dept.
  - Item 3: Erobert, Nicht Befreit! Das deutsche Volk im ersten Besatzungsjahr, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Author: Paul Hagen
  - Item 4: Lohn und Lebenshaltungskosten, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Author: Marga Rohlfing
  - Item 5: Neiderschrift der VerhandlungenGewerkschaftsbundes Hessen, 1946; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Wirtschatliche Vernunft und wirtschaftliche Weisheit, 1947; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Unabhangige Gewerschafts-Organisation / Jugendsekretariat, 1943; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: To the members of the collective bargaining seminar, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Harvard University
    Notes: article; correspondence
  - Item 2: Deuxieme Congres International pour favorises latravailleurs, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Union Internationale pour la Promotion du Travail
  - Item 3: La Remuneration du TravailSalaire: Salaires et PrixStatiques, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Lignes Directrices d'une Reforme Fiscale, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Developments Inside Russia and Eastern Europe, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Economic Bulletin for Europe, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The European Labor MovementTheories: SuggestedReadings, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Modern France: Problems of the Third and Fourth Republics, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Author: E.M. Earle
  - Item 5: Producteurs (L'Economie de l'Entreprise/Le Calculd'Amsterdam), 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Producteurs (Prix Normal et Coutprofit/L'imputation des depenses), 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Producteurs (Prix Normal et Coutprofit/L'imputation des depenses), 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Producteurs (Realisation des Primes d'Entreprise: Lespas faire), 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Rapport Interimaire: Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Author: Mission de Productivite, Etude desRemuneration
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: L'Entreprise Moderne, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Le Travail Personnel du Chef d'Entreprise, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Paul Robin, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Statuts: Deposes a la Prefecture de la Seine en 1937Mai 1951, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: Confederation Generale des Cadres
  - Item 5: Convention Collective National du Personnel SedentaireLibres, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: Federation des Employes et Cadres
  - Item 6: Convention Collective Nationale de Travail du Personnel des Banques, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Conventions Collectives et Conflits Collectifs du Travail: La1951, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: Questions Pratiques
  - Item 8: Ingenieurs et Cadres a la Convention Collectivel'Industrie Textile, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: La Convention Collective et le Droit Public Francais, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: La Regime des Conventions, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Le Patronat Francais et les Conventions Collectives, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Reflexions sur l'Arbitrage, 1951; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The WFTU Campaigns for Social Security, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: World Federation of Trade Unions
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Comment le Parti Communiste dirige la C.G.T., 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Is French Labor Communist?, 1948; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Le Metallo Autonome, 1952; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Le Monde Apres 150 Ans de Technique, 1952; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Productivite et Plein-Emploi: Rapport Interimaire, 1952; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Mission de Productivite
  - Item 6: Stalin's Hold on French Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: To the members of economics 284, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Leon Jouhaux, 1954; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A French Shoe Factory, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Author: Jacques Etevenon
  - Item 2: Remuneration du Travail II, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Situation du Marche du Travail et du Chomage Secouru, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Ministere du Travail et de la Securite Sociale
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining in Postwar Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Notes: article - reprinted from the Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science
  - Item 3: Reflections on the History of the French and AmericanMovements, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Problematique de l'Evolution du Syndicalisme, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Young Comrade, Listen to the Voice of your Brothers, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Etude de la Structure des Offres et DemandesOctobre 1956, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Secretariat d'Etat au Travail et a la Securite Sociale
  - Item 7: Etude du Marche de l'Emploi et du Chomage Secouru, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Etude du Marche de l'Emploi et du Chomage Secouru, 1956; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Box: 10, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Etude du Marche de l'Emploi et du Chomage Secouru, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Marche du Travail: Juillet 1956, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Notes: maps
  - Item 3: The Most Recent Renault Agreement, 1958; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: XXXV Congres Corporatif National: Rapport d'Activite deSociaux, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: XXXV Congres Corporatif National: Rapport d'Activite etAgricoles, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: XXXV Congres Corporatif National: Rapport Moral, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: XXXV Congres Corporatif National: Rapport sur la Dureel'Emploi, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: XXXV Congres Corporatif National: Rapport sur le Marche commun, 1957; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Marche du Travail: Janvier 1956, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Box: 10, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Voraussetzungen einer Arbeiterbildung, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Author: Arbeit und Leben
  - Item 2: Die CGT, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: German Trade Union Federation for the Federal RepublicBerlin, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Notes: chart
  - Item 4: The Educational Activities within the German FederationUnions, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Author: Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund
- Box: 10, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Armistice and Germany's Food Supply 1918-1919, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Author: Bernhard Menne
  - Item 2: Der Streik in der Herrenkleiderkonfektion, 1903; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Box: 10, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: zzz[Empty as of 22Jun78], 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Accord sur l'Exercice du Droit Syndical, 1975; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Regie Nationale des Usines Renault
  - Item 3: Accord d'Entreprise du 29 Decembre 1962, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: International Differences in the Strike PropensityFour Countries, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Job Protection in France and Britain, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Frederic Meyers
  - Item 6: Job Reinstatement: France and the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Labor Organizations and Politics in Belgium and France, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: L'Accord a Vivre de Renault, 1989; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: On Democracy in France, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Henry Walter Ehrmann
  - Item 10: Universite de Paris, Institute des Science SocialesSuperieure, 1965; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Universite de Paris
  - Item 11: Vers un manifeste mondial pour les travailleuses, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Conference Interntionale sur les problemes feminins
  - Item 12: Bierville 1966, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Institut Confederal d'Etudes et de Formation
  - Item 13: La Commune de Paris, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Box: 10, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Le Syndicalisme Vivant: L'Actualite de la Charte D'Amiens, 1959; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: L'Union des Syndicalistes
  - Item 2: Letter From Paris, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Bilan Social d'Entreprise, 1978; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Nationalization and Workers Control in Britain and France, 1953; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Collective agreement of December 29, 1962 between The Management of The Renault Enterprises, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: Renault Enterprises
  - Item 6: Collective agreement of January 3, 1967 between The National Management of Renault Enterprises, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Collective Agreement of November 30, 1982 for the Renault Company, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: Renault Company
  - Item 8: Collective Agreement of November 30, 1982 for the Renault Company, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: The Ben Barka Scandal, 1966; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: George Herald
  - Item 10: Comment defendre les travailleurs dans les entreprises, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: Force Ouvriere Informations
- Box: 10, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Job Security in Three Countries, 1961; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Author: Fred Meyers
  - Item 2: Labor Organizations in Belgium and France, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: What Does De Gaulle Really Want?, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Accord Relatif a l'Excercice du Droit Syndicaldu Personnel, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Accord de Participation, 1978; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Accord d'Entreprise du 30 Novembre 1982, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Discours de M. Dino Del Bo, Presidentdevant le.a Strasbourg, 1964; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)